var questions = {
    q1:{
        question: "What weather phenomenon causes more deaths in the U.S. annually than any other except lightning?",
        choices: ["Tornados", "Hurricanes", "Snowstorms", "Hail"],
        answer: "Tornados"
    },
    q2:{
        question: "What is given to wood whose normal cells have been replaced with mineral deposits?",
        choices: ["Petrified Wood", "Stone Timber", "Rock Lumber", "Gravel Wood"],
        answer: "Petrified Wood"
    },
    q3:{
        question: "What is pollination by birds is called?",
        choices: ["Autogamy", "Ornithophily", "Entomophily", "Anemophily"],
        answer: "Ornithophily"
    },
    q4:{
        question: "Unlike rodents, rabbits have how many incisor teeth?",
        choices: ["Two", "Three", "Four", "Six"],
        answer: "Four"
    },
    q5:{
        question: "What percent of fire-related deaths are due to smoke inhalation rather than burns?",
        choices: ["10%", "50%", "80%", "99%"],
        answer: "80%"
    },
    q6:{
        question: "To what familiar fruit is the plantain similar?",
        choices: ["Mangos", "Bananas", "Kiwi", "Papaya"],
        answer: "Bananas"
    },
    q7:{
        question: "What U.S. President was recognized as a world authority on American game animals?",
        choices: ["Theodore Roosevelt", "Thomas Jefferson", "Dwight Eisenhower", "Woodrow Wilson"],
        answer: "Theodore Roosevelt"
    },
    q8:{
        question: "How many men have walked on the moon?",
        choices: ["Eight", "Ten", "Twelve", "Fourteen"],
        answer: "Twelve"
    },
    q9:{
        question: "What is the fastest-running terrestrial animal?",
        choices: ["Cheetah", "Lion", "Dog", "Jaguar"],
        answer: "Cheetah"
    },
    q10:{
        question: "In what country do the greatest number of tornadoes occur?",
        choices: ["United States", "China", "Canada", "Russia"],
        answer: "United States"
    }
};